bytephoto.com 2014-06-19

# Home - Privacy Policy

PRIVACY POLICY  
Your privacy on the Internet is important to us. As part of the operation of BytePhoto.Com, we gather certain types of information about our users, and we would like to explain the types of information we gather, what we do with it and how to correct or change the information.

BytePhoto.Com collects two types of data from users: volunteered personal data (such as names, e-mail addresses, etc.); and aggregated data (such as information about traffic patterns on BytePhoto.Com).

PERSONAL DATA  
Personal data is collected when users provide personal data to BytePhoto.Com, for example in registering for membership services, in answering surveys, requesting information, and purchasing items from BytePhoto.Com. 

In accepting any prize from BytePhoto your contact information will be conveyed to the awarding Sponsor and you give them the right to contact you.

AGGREGATED INFORMATION  
Aggregated information, such as which pages users access or visit and information volunteered by users, such as survey information and/or site registrations, is collected through various methods. For example, BytePhoto.Com collects IP addresses. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you're surfing the Web. Web servers, the computers that “serve up” Web pages, automatically identify your computer by its IP address, and when you request a page from BytePhoto.Com, our servers log your IP address. BytePhoto.Com collects IP addresses for the purposes of system administration and security logging.

USE OF COOKIES  
BytePhoto.Com also uses “cookies” to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that most major Web sites write to your hard drive for record keeping purposes when you visit them. Cookies allow BytePhoto.Com to measure activity on the Site and to improve your user experience, for example, by remembering your passwords and viewing preferences, thus allowing you to visit various member-only parts of the Site without reregistering. Cookies are used by BytePhoto.Com to measure activity on the Site and make improvements and updates based on which areas are popular and which are not. BytePhoto.Com does not use cookies to retrieve information from your computer that was not originally sent in a cookie. BytePhoto.Com does not use information transferred through cookies for any promotional or marketing purposes, nor is that information shared with any third parties whatsoever. You may occasionally get cookies from our advertisers, which is standard in the Internet industry. BytePhoto.Com does not control these cookies, and these cookies are not subject to BytePhoto.com's privacy policies. In addition, BytePhoto displays Google Ads. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to this site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you'd prefer, you can set yours to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent. However, it is possible that some parts of the Site will not function properly if you do so.

USE OF INFORMATION COLLECTED BY BYTEPHOTO.COM  
BytePhoto.com uses both the personal and aggregated information we collect for multiple purposes. The information is used to improve the content of the Site, to customize the content and/or layout of the Site for each individual user and to notify users about updates to the Site or promotional offers or opportunities that we believe will be of interest to you. BytePhoto.com will share aggregated information with third parties for both advertising and promotional purposes.

BytePhoto.com does not share your personal information with third parties without your permission.

HOW TO UNSUBSCRIBE FROM NEWSLETTERS  
If you'd rather not receive newsletters via e-mail, simply: Go to BytePhoto.com and select the Newsletter > Subscription tab in the Home Menu, complete the Newsletter Unsubscribe box -or- send an email to [admin@bytephoto.com](mailto:admin@bytephoto.com) requesting removal (include the email address that you wish to unsubscribe if other than the sender email) You may also manage any Newsletter subscription using the link at the bottom of the Newsletter.

CHILDREN AND PRIVACY  
BytePhoto.Com encourages parents and guardians to spend time with their children online, and to be fully familiar with the sites visited by their children. No information should be submitted to or posted on the Site by users under the age of 13 without the consent of their parent or guardian. 

LINKS TO OTHER SITES  
It is important to note that BytePhoto.Com contains links to sites other than BytePhoto.Com, and that those sites may not follow the same privacy policies as BytePhoto.Com. For instance, if you click on an advertisement on BytePhoto.Com, this will take you away from BytePhoto.Com and to an entirely different site. This can include links from advertisers, content providers and partners who may use BytePhoto.Com's logo and/or style as a result of a co-branding agreement. These sites may send their own cookies to you, and may collect data and make uses of it that BytePhoto.Com would not.

BytePhoto.Com reserves the right to change this policy at any time by notifying users of the existence of a revised privacy policy. You can e-mail us with any further questions at [admin@bytephoto.com](mailto:admin@bytephoto.com).
